<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Warangal App</string>

    <array name="list_icon">
        <item>R.drawable.hanamkonda</item>
        <item>R.drawable.thousandpillar</item>
        <item>R.drawable.warangalfort</item>
        <item>R.drawable.ramapa</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="list_titles">
        <item>Hanamkonda</item>
        <item>Thousand Pillar</item>
        <item>Warangal Fort</item>
        <item>Ramapa</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="warangal_fort">        In the early 13th century during the reign of Ganapatideva, the capital was moved from Hanamkonda to the new city of Warangal,
	which was laid out in a circular plan with three concentric rings of walls. The first ring which constitutes the Fort has high walls made of
	massive granite blocks laid without mortar. Inner faces of the walls have steps ascending to a path that runs along the top.
	Entrance gateways like the one seen here were renovated in Bahmani times as is clear from the sculpted fragments reused from
	dismantled temples. Here a temple ceiling fragment is placed in a niche. The image is of Vishnu carried by Garuda
	and surrounded by attendants. Above this some granite blocks are replaced by panels of elephants and yali.</string>
    <string name="drawerOpen">Open</string>
    <string name="drawerClose">Close</string>
    <string name="about">         Warangal About this sound pronunciation  is a city and district headquarters of Warangal district in the Indian state of Telangana.
 Warangal is located 148 kilometres (92 mi) northeast of the state capital of Hyderabad and is the administrative headquarters of
 Warangal District. Warangal area is a combination of Warangal, Hanmakonda and Kazipet. Warangal is the second-biggest city
 after Hyderabad in Telangana. It is well known for heritage and has been included in the scheme of Heritage City Development
 and Augmentation Yojana (HRIDAY) along with eleven other cities of the country.[8] It is also selected in the finalized list of
 100 proposed smart cities by  NDA government with the view of developing urban infrastructure and industrial investment in the
 listed cities.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Section 1</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Section 2</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Section 3</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string-array name="tab_name">
        <item>History</item>
        <item>Gallery</item>
        <item>Tickets</item>
        <item>Contact</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
